{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388787022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388787022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388824041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388824041"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 77faed99-deed-4130-9d5c-43efb4c66b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388828632","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388828631"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 77faed99-deed-4130-9d5c-43efb4c66b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388830881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388830881"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 77faed99-deed-4130-9d5c-43efb4c66b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388862835","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388862835"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 77faed99-deed-4130-9d5c-43efb4c66b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388887499","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388887499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 77faed99-deed-4130-9d5c-43efb4c66b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388914586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388914585"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 77faed99-deed-4130-9d5c-43efb4c66b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388914682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388914682"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 77faed99-deed-4130-9d5c-43efb4c66b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388935162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388935161"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 77faed99-deed-4130-9d5c-43efb4c66b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388948410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388948410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-7-8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388955371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388955371"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-6-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388963360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388963360"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-6-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388976833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388976833"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-8-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388983246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388983246"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388991531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388991531"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549388999194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549388999194"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-9-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389005010","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389005010"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-0"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389013514","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389013514"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389027171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389027171"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-6-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389033867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389033866"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" cdbdd3d9-2267-41b2-93fb-bd6ef5f6871a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-6-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389095186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389095186"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389104611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389104611"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389106248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389106248"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389127549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389127549"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389129159","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389129158"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389137208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389137207"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389138792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389138792"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389144037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389144036"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389146064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389146064"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389146217","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389146217"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389263369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389263369"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 4fab1ed7-5d58-4848-8c9c-57223e75ffaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389263435","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389263435"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 3ab3f8cb-5c89-4c2b-90df-0a72c8f7c504"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu amemfuga ng'ombe mmoja anayeitwa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389282930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389282930"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-o-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389288543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389288542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-e-a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389293395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389293395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-e-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389299470","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389299470"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-i-o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389304914","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389304914"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389340850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389340850"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_o-a-i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389346975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389346975"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_o-a-i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389353414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389353414"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_o-i-u"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389357316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389357316"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389362634","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389362634"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_e-i-a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389370514","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389370514"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-i-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389376275","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389376274"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" faa8cf08-332b-47b9-ae7b-a9d8b87728cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-i-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389396686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389396686"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_0_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389403577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389403576"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_1_4_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389410647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389410647"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_0_2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389417760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389417760"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_8_4_3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389424699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389424698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_6_4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389431910","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389431910"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_2_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389439986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389439985"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_2_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389447220","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389447218"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_9_6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389454400","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389454399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_6_5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389461601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389461601"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_8_9_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389468604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389468603"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_9_3_2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389482490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389482483"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 1cae34a6-9270-4e6d-a008-8d25d8cb17c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_9_3_2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389494522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389494521"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-e-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389498510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389498510"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389502705","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389502705"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-u-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389507553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389507552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-o-u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389511750","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389511749"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-e-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389515851","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389515851"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-o-i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389523553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389523553"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-u-o"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389528373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389528372"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389532789","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389532789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-o-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389537203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389537202"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_o-i-u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389543414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389543411"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 40698375-4900-4199-9723-b9b2338622b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_o-i-u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389596365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389596364"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 3de71a26-9289-423b-8893-d5c3130619e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mwalimu-ndugu-kabisa-msituni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" msituni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549389625287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549389625284"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190205_204556"," gameId":" 3de71a26-9289-423b-8893-d5c3130619e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mrembo-umri-macho-msituni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" msituni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}